A resignation.
I’ve never resigned from anything in my life.
This is hard for me.
I’ll lose my connection with Takeshi-san.
But I think Takeshi-san said once that he’d like his wife to be at home.
Why am I saying these things?
Maybe the truth is that I’m not a good woman.
I’m not the decent person I thought I was.
Maybe I’m a fraud and my faults are coming out.
I suppose I had self-control enough to manage myself so far.
When I think about it, maybe I am unstable now.
Lain is the one that seems to have it together.
It sounds like a bad joke.
I’ve failed.
It’s not right for Lain to come for help from someone like me.
There’s no excuse for it.
It’s over when I start making mistakes concerning my work.
I’ll have to discuss it tomorrow.