I received a phone call from Harumi today.
I don’t hear from her often. She’s a bit lazy about making phone calls.
I was surprised to hear from her.
But I was really surprised when Harumi told me that she was getting married.
She always used to talk about how she just broke up with a guy and felt like she wanted to die, or that she wanted to be introduced to a new guy.
She calls so infrequently.
I was wondering why she called, and it was about marriage.
I felt sort of relieved and slightly shocked.
But when a woman is 26 years old, it’s not odd for her to be married or to have children.
Ohh!
Now I’m feeling jealous.
That’s okay.
When I go to the wedding, I’ll introduce Takeshi-san and make her jealous.
Maybe I’ll get married soon, too.
I'll call Takeshi-san tomorrow.