Oh, what a surprise!
To run into Yoshida-kun at a place like that.
I thought that it was weird for a guy to be buying underwear alone.
Maybe he was shopping for his girlfriend.
I feel embarrassed.
It was nice to talk to him, though, and I have nothing to worry about.
I guess I’ve been stressed lately.
I sure ran my mouth with Yoshida-kun.
I think I bothered him.
Well, there’s no sense in regretting it now.
Yoshida-kun does seem very grown up for his age.
He surprised me.
He’s not as grown up as Takeshi-san, though.
He said, "Touko-san, you seem tired." He was gentle, and I was a bit touched.
No, no, Touko.
Yoshida-kun was just feeling sorry for you.
Ohh.
Maybe his girlfriend saw him talking to me and got angry at him.
Aww. I should apologize him next time I see him.
He seems so cheerful at the lab.
He said that he’ll bring some sample medical utensils next time he swings by.
I’ll get over my stress soon.