Lain gave me a present.
It was for my birthday and also for Valentine’s Day coming up.
She gave me cookies to go with my tea.
She said that she made the cookies with her mother because she knew that I like something with my tea.
What are you doing getting so emotional over a client, Touko?
What are you doing getting so moved by a client, Touko?
Maybe it’s because Takeshi-san didn’t give me a birthday present.
That was terrible of you, Takeshi-san.
Lately I’ve been moody.
I suddenly become sad or depressed.
Is it because I’m getting older?
But how did Lain know my birthday?
Did I tell her?
I don’t suppose it matters.
It’s the first time I’ve received a gift from a girl, though.
It’s a bit embarrassing.
Thank you, Lain.