Today on my way home from the lab, I ran into Yoshida-kun.
Lately, I had been so busy with helping Professor Takashima that I didn’t have time to talk to Yoshida-kun even when he visited the lab.
He seems to have been worried about me, and was waiting for me at the lab until I was through with work.
I don't want him to be too kind to me right now, when I’m feeling so irritable.
I feel like blaming someone for what’s been going on, and I feel that if someone is kind to me, my feelings for Takeshi-san will crumble.
Yoshida-kun just quietly walked me home, but he made me very happy.
There was a "me" that was happy then.
No.
I shouldn’t feel this way.
Takeshi-san is the one I like.
Any woman would be happy if a attractive guy like him was nice to her, wouldn't she?
Takeshi-san... I want you to catch me.
I really am tired.
I think I should use RML a little longer.