I became emotional at Harumi’s wedding.
I’ve never seen her look so pretty.
She said she was going on her honeymoon to have a baby right away.
I’m glad that she seemed so happy.
I love to see wedding dresses.
Weddings in churches are so romantic.
There were over 100 invited people attending the reception.
I’ve never been to such a large wedding crowd.
Oh, when will I be as happy as Harumi?
It was unfortunate that although there were many people at the wedding who knew each other, there weren’t many people for me to talk to.
And Takeshi-san couldn’t come.
Kanoko couldn’t, either.
I know that people living in a society like this have a lot of things they have to do, but I feel that they should make time to go to their friend’s wedding.
Ah, well.
I shouldn’t complain.
I’d want all my friends to attend my wedding.
I guess I really do want to get married.