I met Lain for the second time today.
She looked right at me and called me "sensei." That made me feel good, and I blushed.
I wonder if I’ve become transparent to her already.
I must be an inexperienced counselor if I blush just from being called sensei.
From the first time I met Lain, I had an unusual sense about her.
I wonder what that was.
When I look into her eyes, I feel as though she can see right through me.
Do I, reflected in her large eyes, look unreliable to her?
I don’t remember myself being as calm as Lain when I was her age.
I was more of a "polite" character, so I guess I was fine.
She seems really composed.
They say that kids are getting all precocious these days.
I guess times are changing.
Ah!
Now I’m talking like an old woman.
Don’t let the hallucinations get you down, Lain!
I'm going to help you feel better.