Welcome home, Touko.
I’m so tired today.
I don’t like the atmosphere of Japanese research centers.
Why do Japanese research centers feel like this?
The people entirely lack a critical mentality, and they are lazy.
I wish they would stop looking at me judgmentally just because I studied abroad.
Research centers in America weren’t like this.
I suppose they think I was able to study abroad because my dad has connections.
Everybody is so icy here.
When I was in grade school, we were so welcoming of kids transferring from other schools.
Maybe we change when we grow up.
This makes me depressed, but it’s what I have to face now.
I can’t live like I did in America forever.
If I do what I’m supposed to do, people will give me credit eventually.
Okay, Touko?
Soon I’ll have my examination to become a counselor.
Until I finish that exam, I’ll have to bear with it the best I can.