Today I took a walk with Takeshi-san along the Charles River.
I reflected on the four years that I’ve spent here.
At first I was elated, but things were tough until I met Takeshi-san.
I think I’ve changed a lot since I met him.
I suppose it wasn’t time for romance, but being alone was a downer.
When you feel down you want someone to be around you.
But it doesn’t mean that you ought to seek out a boyfriend thoughtlessly just because you’re feeling sad.
I’ve gotten my feelings hurt a few times that way.
But Takeshi-san is different.
I feel safe just being with him.
I think it’s the first time I’ve felt this way.
Next year, Takeshi-san will return to Japan and start working at a research center.
What will happen to me?
I would love to work in the same research center as Takeshi-san.