The ring that Yoshida-kun bought me... Could this be... he gave it to me without saying anything.
But that’s okay.
I won’t make the same mistake.
I haven’t produced any research results either.
My own pride won’t let me leave my work at the lab now.
I asked Lain a dumb question today.
I asked her, "Who are you?
Are you really Lain?" Without changing her expression but looking upward, she said, "I’m me."
A question with such an obvious answer.
Still, before even thinking about it, my mouth was open.
I wonder why.
I think Lain is probably tired of it, too.
I know.
It has to do with the girl I’ve been seeing in my dreams lately who looks a lot like Lain.
She looks like Lain, but she isn’t her.
I better straighten my mind out.
Otherwise I won’t be much of a counselor.