I can’t get out of my head Lain's eyes, and it makes me feel uneasy.
Will you stop, Lain?
Don’t look at me like that!
Nothing’s wrong with me.
At least not in front of you.
Lain looks at me as if she can see through me completely.
I remember feeling that way when I first met Lain.
She can see that I’m using her as an object for research.
No!
How can that be?
What can she know?
I’m the one with the problem.
I’m not present as a counselor.
This can’t continue.
It’s at times like this when I have to immerse myself on my work.
But when I was feeling unstable, Lain just looked at me, saying nothing.
She had a faint smile on her face.
Something is wrong with her!
What is she trying to do?
Why can’t someone else take care of her instead of me?
I keep saying that she isn’t sick.
Let me check one more time.
I feel so uncomfortable.