I’m making a diary entry for the first time in a long while.
Even though I've missed some, I'm proud that I've kept it up for this long.
Lately I’ve been coming home from work and going right to bed.
Still, it seems that by using the equipment Yoshida-kun gave me, I feel rested in the morning even though I go to bed exhausted.
I’m still tired, though.
I’m psychologically tired.
Why do I have to work like a dog so that Professor Takashima can publish his articles?
It might look as if I have less work to do because I have only one client: Lain.
It’s true that things are going well with Lain, and that may make it seem as though I have less to do, too.
But lately, I’ve been feeling harassed.
Why have I been feeling so irritable lately?
I hate it.