Lately I’ve been seeing bad dreams.
I dreamed that I married Yoshida-kun and that Takeshi-san was saddened by it.
I looked at Takeshi-san and started to laugh.
These aren’t the kind of things that I would want.
Maybe there’s a part of my subconscious where I want these things.
But I don’t want my child to look exactly like Lain.
I think that Lain is a good girl, but I don’t want my own child to be like her.
Why?
Why, Touko?
I don’t know, but I can’t love her.
I just can’t approve of it.
What am I really thinking?
I’m losing confidence in my own feelings.
More and more I can’t tell reality apart from my dreams.
Is this a delusion, too?
Am I seeing hallucinations?
That can’t be.
I’ve become psychologically hypersensitive.
You’re okay, Touko.
I should use the new machine Yoshida-kun gave me.
Since he helped me, I should at least repay him by cooperating with his experiments.
If I lose him now.
I’ll be in a horrible place psychologically.
I can’t go to a horrible place now.