I’m home!
I’m back in Japan after 5 years.
Hee, hee.
Japan is great.
Living in America was good, but I feel at ease being back home.
I’m a bit scared, though.
When you come home after being away for so long, you start to feel out of place.
I remember being insecure in junior high school, too.
I would be tardy for school and Mom scolded me.
Five years sure went by fast.
I had no time to be homesick.
But you worked really hard, didn't you, Touko?
Study, study, study.
I made good friends, and there were good times and bad times, too.
I had a romance that didn’t work out, but I had another romance that worked out well.
Looking back, I wonder what about me changed the most.
Hee, hee.
I’m okay, I’m okay!
Have self-confidence and fight, Touko!
I start working at the research center tomorrow.
I want to stop worrying today.
When I go to the research center tomorrow, I might see Takeshi-san.