Today was really busy.
I got to have lunch with Takeshi-san, though.
He didn’t look well today.
He seemed fidgety and said that he didn’t have much time.
I wonder if he’s very busy in the research room where he works.
Could it be that he doesn’t like me anymore?
That can't be it, right?
He said that he can’t go to Harumi’s wedding with me.
I wanted to show him off to Harumi so much.
It’s too bad.
I wonder if he's being cautious with me because I have wishful thinking about marriage.
I’ve heard that that sort of thing can happen.
But I wanted to at least have a relaxed lunch with him.
I can't help it if he's busy, though.
You just have to hang in there, Touko.
I don’t want to be thought of as a selfish person, either.
But if Takeshi-san stopped liking me, I don’t think I could go on living.
Well, that’s not completely true.
It’s too bad that I can’t see him for two more weeks.
Proceed carefully, Touko.