I wonder how many times I’ve met with Lain up till now.
It seems that she sometimes has hallucinations, but they don’t seem to be developing further.
I think that seeing hallucinations must be a very difficult thing for her.
She’s not the kind of child that should have a gloomy personality.
I wonder if she is getting a hard time at school.
Her mother told me that she isn’t being bullied.
When I mention school, Lain tends to become quiet.
Maybe I should ask some of her friends at school how she’s doing.
I think the kind of bullying that happens in schools now is different from the kind that took place when I was younger.
I wish I could help you, Lain.
I feel depressed when I see Lain.
It can’t be helped when I get depressed, but it’s just at those times that Professor Takashima complains to me about trifling matters.
Ahh!
Tomorrow I have the day off.
I’ll go on the town and relax.