Oh, I’m so sick of all this work!
I really hate Professor Takashima.
There are other researchers he could delegate to.
I’ve been in a bad mood lately.
I haven’t been able to see Takeshi-san, there hasn't been any new counseling work, and I’ve just been doing menial chores.
It's really putting me on edge.
Nothing's going my way.
I can't be cranky.
I’m a counselor.
I’m sorry, Lain.
I have to think of my work outside of counseling as part of my work, too.
I have to do what I have to do, and I want to be recognized.
Otherwise, I’ll fail.
Come to think of it, it will be Halloween soon.
Back in America, people getting ready for Halloween made every day feel like a festival.
Those were the good days.
I guess this year there won’t be Halloween or Christmas, either.