Just when I thought I was able to meet Yoshida-kun, I screwed it up!
He said that he was waiting at the department store, talking to the person in charge of health equipment.
Oh, I’m such a careless person.
He suddenly apologized to me.
Yoshida-kun was probably angry.
Ahh.
I’ve done something embarrassing again.
He was just bringing the health equipment he promised to bring.
The machine he brought looked like one of those cheap pulse massagers for relaxation.
Though, it seemed to be from a legit manufacturer, so I wonder if it actually works?
It's made by a legitimate medical company, so I kind of feel like it'll work.
He said that it works better if I do it every day, not only  when I'm tired.
I bet Yoshida-kun gets girlfriends easily.
He’s such a good-looking guy and he’s tall.
When he comes to the lab, all the women seem to really take notice of him.
Oh, what am I thinking?
I already have Takeshi-san.
I want to see Takeshi-san.