Lately at the lab, people seem to be looking at me more critically than before.
If someone wants to say something, let him say it.
Still, this bothers me.
When I glance at people, I can see them whispering and laughing.
I suppose its just more stupid rumors about me, but I wonder if I’m the only cheerful person working here.
I had my first date with Takeshi-san in a long time, but I was so inattentive.
It seemed like Takeshi-san had something to say, but I felt like I had a big hole in the middle of my chest.
What’s wrong, Touko?
Are you tired?
Lately, Professor Takashima has had me digging around for documents. Maybe that’s worn me out.
He can have someone else look for documents.
What can I do?
That’s how things are done in Japan.
I think I should have stayed in America.
I’ll use Yoshida-kun’s health equipment again tonight.
Sometimes it makes me sleepy.
I wonder if it really works.
I haven’t seen it advertised much.
I heard that it’s still being used on an experimental basis.