There will be a party at a friend’s home tomorrow, so I made an apple pie.
When I gave Takeshi-san a slice, he said that the pie was so sweet that everyone at the party except for him would love it.
He said that my baking had become Americanized.
It’s true that compared to the cakes and pies in America, Japanese desserts are usually much less sweet.
At first I didn’t bake things this sweet.
But now, I feel that unless I make my desserts sweet, they won't be good enough.
If I get used to all this sweet stuff, I won’t want to eat pastries when I return to Japan.
If I don’t cool it I could get fat and Takeshi-san won’t like me.
I’ll have to start another diet tomorrow!
Hee, hee.