Today I met with Kanako, one of my "naughty" friends from college.
Good going, Touko!
I asked about taking her to Harumi’s wedding, but she said that she might not be able to because she is busy with work.
How uncaring!
I haven’t seen Kanako since I left for America, so I really wanted to get together with her.
Kanako asked if my birthday will be coming up soon.
She’s right.
They say that things go fast for a woman once she’s past twenty years old.
How true.
I’m already 27.
Harumi will get married in September.
I wonder what Takeshi-san is thinking.
What will I do for my birthday this year?
Ahh!
Maybe I will propose to him!
But then again, maybe not.