Today I met with Kyoko-chan, one of Lain’s classmates from grade school.
She’s in middle school now.
She’s at a point of life when people start to take interest in many things.
I was glad to have met with her.
She was ordinary.
She is ordinary.
She goes out shopping with friends and talks with boys she likes.
She’s an ordinary girl.
Lain is not an ordinary girl.
And who is Misato-chan?
Is she the same as Minako-chan?
That can’t be.
I don’t understand.
What am I doing by following up on all these things and telling lies?
This has nothing to do with my research.
My job as a psychiatrist and a counselor was to diagnose and treat someone.
This existence called Lain seems to be a kind of vacancy.
Does Lain have a problem, or do I?