Nice to meet you. Order whatever you want.
Lain doesn’t go out much, and it’s hard to tell if she’s dating anyone.
Sometimes she helps me with my schoolwork, and I offer to take her out and have some fun to thank her, but she never comes.
A royal chocolate parfait, please.
And who did you say you were?
I’m her tutor.
Oh... a tutor.
That’s why she’s so smart.
I’ll start on my parfait.
I really like their parfaits here.
But what did you want to talk about?
Well, what is she like at school? What kind of girl is she, from your point of view?
Lain is a quiet girl.
She doesn’t stand out too much and she doesn’t have too many friends.
She’s smart, though.
She got a really good grade on one of her papers.
Some complicated subject.
Kaori couldn’t understand it.