We were in the same class in 5th and 6th grade.
We were in the same group because we sat close to each other.
She was quiet, so she didn’t talk to many kids besides me.
She was like a sister to me.
We didn’t play together much, though.
When would you say that Lain started to change?
She wasn't so gloomy until about a year ago.
When I see her these days, we don’t have much to talk about.
It’s too bad, but lately, she’s just another classmate to me.
Have you talked to her at all recently?
Recently? I feel like there was something. I wonder what it was...
Can you remember?
That's weird. I usually have a good memory.
Do you remember talking about shopping or boys?
No. I don’t think we talked about that.