February 7th. Interview for testimony from a witness to the suicide of a high school girl.
Before we begin questioning, I’d like to confirm your identity.
Shinji Makino, 29 years old.
Office worker.
Is that correct?
Could you state your address?
Sure. Shinagawa ward, Kamiosaki, 30-19-105, Meguro-residence 504.
Thank you.
This interview will be recorded, by the way, but it will be kept confidential, so please don’t worry.
Alright.
Let’s get started.
Could you tell me what you saw at the scene of the suicide in as much detail as possible?
Where do you want me to start? From the morning of that day?
No. Just what you remember from around the time of the suicide. Relax. Don’t feel pressured.
Uhh.