Hello, Makino-san.
It’s been a while.
You don’t seem to be doing very well, so I’ll keep this short.
Can you take responsibility for the things you say to us from now on?
Makino-san?
I haven’t been able to sleep. I feel better when I’m looking at the computer.
Smoking isn’t really allowed here, but if it relaxes you, go ahead.
Let’s begin.
The reason you’re here...
It’s about Lain.
Yes it is. Did you meet her after the shooting?
Probably.
Probably?
I don’t know anymore.
Detective, could you contact a psychiatrist for me?
I can’t take it anymore.
I don’t want to die, but all of a sudden, I want to die now!
Look at these scars!
There’s nowhere left to cut!
This is interrogation room number 7.
Bring a doctor here quickly.
This one’s no good, either.
Hey, cut it out!
Sorry.
Forget about the doctor.
Bring a cleaner.
And a cup of coffee, too.