You were there as a twosome.
Yeah. So?
Well, according to a storekeeper who saw you, the girl you were with was very young.
Yeah. And?
Well, you see, prostitution takes place at that store.
Sorry to tell you, but I don’t have any hobbies like that. She’s just a girl I knew.
Is that right? Well, I’d also like to ask her a few questions too.
I haven’t had any contact with her, and why do I have to do all this for you anyway?
Because we’d like to have as much information as we can to understand why a high school student is dead.
We haven’t even been able to retrieve the gun used in the crime.
And you think she took it with her? You’ve got to be kidding. She’s in junior high school!
We’re not certain, we’re just not ruling out the possibility.
Among the people at that store at that time, the only person who we haven’t been able to identify is the girl you were with.
Could you help us out with more detailed information?