I don't want to talk if my testimony is going to harm her.
No, nothing has been decided yet.
We’d just like to be able to contact her.
There’s nothing for you to worry about.
But is there something...
No, nothing.
I did meet her through the Internet.
But she wasn’t the kind of kid that would reveal an e-mail address.
She was good at computers.
What do you mean?
She tapped into computers.
You mean she was a hacker?
No doubt about it.
Then you wouldn’t be able to contact her?
I don’t mean that I couldn’t.
I reached her once.
But I can’t guarantee that she still even has that address.
I see.
Then there’s little we can do.
We’ll handle it from here, then.
Could you give us her address?
Sure, I don’t mind.
If you don’t have it, we can have some of our specialists look into it.
If you do hear from her, could you keep our little meeting here a secret?
It would be important for you, too, that you keep this a secret.
Is that a threat?
Oh, not at all.
We have better things to do than make threats.
As long as we aren’t interfered with, things will be just fine.
That’s what I mean.