It’s horrible, but I can’t do anything about it.
Someone’s been reading my diary.
It’s been copied and displayed on an FTP site with a vulgar title.
I stopped it, but over 20 people have already read it.
Why did this all happen?
Other people can do what I can do.
I think I’ll avoid the net for a while.
I want to see what’s going on, but my diary might be on someone’s site, being reproduced right now.
I know.
I’m going to send an information-deleting engine into the net.
But what if whoever took my diary has the diary’s back-up information, too?
I’m sure the person who took my diary is that gross guy.
And if it’s him, he would certainly have that information.
I’m so mad.
I can’t win this by myself.
So this is what I amount to.
I think I’ll consult Mr. Rabbit.
I wonder what will help.