I started a game on the net.
It’s called the "Mouse Game". You sell tickets to your friends and make money.
But if I start making lots of money, the other players will have a grudge against me.
There will be people who want to kill me then, so I have to be careful.
At first I thought this was just a game, but it made me feel bad after a while, and I wanted to cry.
There was a questionnaire that came with the game asking me what I thought of it, so I wrote the company telling them what I honestly thought.
I guess they know who I am now and don’t like me.
I’m sad.
I don’t like games like that.
I’d rather play a game that everyone can laugh with and enjoy together.
It isn’t for me.