Misato-chan came to visit my house today.
Mom seemed to be in a good mood—sort of.
Misato-chan taught me how to draw.
Mom came and checked in on us often.
Dad, Mom, Misato-chan and I had dinner together.
It was great.
I didn’t learn that much about drawing, but Misato-chan said that she will visit again soon.
We took Misato-chan back to home in Dad’s car.
She has a very fancy house in a rich neighborhood.
It was almost dreamlike.
Misato-chan’s mom came to the door and spoke with Dad a bit.
She was really pretty, like an actress.
I guess that a pretty girls like Misato-chan must come from beautiful mothers like that.
But only a girl like me could come from my kind of Mom.
I’m sorry, Mom.
But I really had fun today.