I talked to Kasumi sensei today.
I believe in Misato-chan, but I wanted to see what was actually going on.
The sensei said that there is an art magazine in America with a painting by a Japanese artist very similar to Misato-chan’s.
I didn’t want to see the magazine, but I wanted to make sure.
The picture in the magazine and Misato-chan’s painting looked alike.
They were more than alike.
I could not tell the difference between the two.
It seems that the Japanese artist who painted it was just a novice, and that it was the first time she won a prize for her artwork.
I searched the Net about it when I got home.
When I got home, I dug around on the Web and found out that his father was a great artist.
Misato-chan would never plagiarize.
Still, the paintings looked so similar.
But I thought that Misato-chan did her work before this other person submitted hers to this magazine.
I’m going to look into it and clear her name.
Sensei said that people often come up with the same ideas at the same time.
It was probably a coincidence. But she also said that there would be problems if it was openly declared.