I was thinking of not seeing Touko-san anymore today.
When I told her about Misato-chan, she said that there are some things that people can’t say, even to those who are closest to them.
Did Misato-chan go away because I was hiding things about myself from her?
Is that why she went away without saying anything to me?
Even if there’s something I can’t say, I would never do that.
Touko-san and Misato-chan are awful.
Nobody understands me.
I don’t feel like doing schoolwork.
Am I a truant?
I don’t want to leave people behind.
I’ve got to fight.
Although they say that I ought to study what interests me, the only things I’m interested in are Misato-chan and myself.
But its over.
I have to find other things that are meaningful to me.