Mom said that she went to my school to ask for a leave of absence.
I thought that I ought to feel glad that I won’t have to go to school, but I’m sad.
I’ve genuinely been separated from society.
I feel that I’ve been rejected by everyone, and I’m sad.
Can't I live an ordinary life anymore?
Dad won’t come home and Mom looks worn out.
Why won’t Dad come home?
Doesn’t he want to see me anymore?
Doesn’t Dad like me anymore?
I want to see him.
I fell asleep weeping, and saw hallucinations again.
It’s scary.
I can see them whether I’m asleep or not.
I can’t believe it myself.
I don’t understand it.
I want someone to prove to me that I am the person that I know I am.
I want to see Dad.
I want to see Dad and hug him.
As he tells me that everything will be fine.