I went to see Touko-san alone because Mom was sleeping in.
I asked Touko-san what she writes about me in her research reports.
She didn't give me a clear answer.
While Touko-san left the room for a while, I took copies of some pages from her notebook.
I thought that I now knew the research data Touko-san keeps about me, and that I knew what she does with it.
I could see that she sends information about me to the research room, and that she sends a lot of it.
Could it be visual data?
Auditory data?
I also noticed some writing that seemed to have daily entries in it.
Could it be a diary?
I couldn't find that data in her ‘host’ page.
Touko-san tends to transmit her data late at night.
I’ll try to access her site then.
She has a very big file about me that would take a long time to download, so I don’t think she’ll find out if I accessed it.
I don’t think Touko-san knows much about machines and computers.
I feel bad because I think I’m tricking Touko-san, but on the other hand, I feel good.