Do you know where I'm going?...
I don't know either.
That's because I'm going to be born soon.
Will I become a more evolved human being?
If I think so I might as well think so.
A human without a body isn't human?
There are people who have bodies that aren't human.
Is that me?
I'm not human?
Lain is Lain.
What is it to be human?
You're human if you have a body?
I'm me.
Am I just conglomerated with my body?
I need a body if I'm going to live in the real world.
Suicide would be stupid.
It would be better to just die naturally.
I don't need it.
I might need it someday.
That might be true.
I won't need a body to live in the Wired.
I'll need the recollections of the body.
How about the recollections of a body that grows older?
My point of view may change?
Is there a need for it to change?
There's no guarantee that that will be you.
Lain, what do I need to be on the Wired?
Existence and will.
The rest is just data.