Clinical notices from last session: First, concerning this case, I want to treat her as a therapist as opposed to a psychiatrist.
Therefore, I will treat Iwakura Lain as my client from now on.
One of the reasons for this is that she is still 12 years old and is emotionally sensitive.
I do not want to make her feel that she is sick.
In fact, from the results of her last clinical visit, the extent of what she is troubled from is nightmares and psychological damage associated with it.
Although during sessions with her, psychological discomfort can be detected, she is able to ask and answer questions without a problem.
I see no reason to advocate objections to my conclusion that she is sick, but at this point, I would like to treat her as someone without a mental illness.
One more thing: Because I am both a psychiatrist and a counselor, my job is selecting the best position possible for my patients.
When counseling her in the future, if I detect symptoms of mental illness, I would have to treat her as a psychiatrist.
Of course, there’s a good chance that I myself will continue to treat her.
In order to honor my research and keep it objective, I may want to ask a third party to continue to treat her clinically.
In the meanwhile, I will continue to work with her in a research setting.
This may be an exceptional situation at this research center, but I would like to proceed with it.