At this stage, I thought it would be a bad idea to ask her about her symptoms in a teasing fashion.
I was unable to find details concerning her symptoms.
However, she generally seems to be a clever and relaxed girl.
Her mother showed me a painting she did in school.
It was very well painted, and showed a high level of artistic sensibility.
However, there were no elements in it that could complement the analysis of the patient.
At this stage, she appears to be at a delusional state, but there seems be a very good chance that she is a normal child.
One point from her physical examination struck me.
Her vision is excellent.
Her standard light reflex is lower than the standard range.
However, I have not seen in her the type of dermatological or anemic problems that are common in kids with this condition.