What kind of research do you do?
Research? I never mentioned that...
But this is a research center, isn’t it?
I’m still an apprentice. I haven’t done any of my own research.
You’re an apprentice after being here for 3 years?
How did you know...
You told me yourself.
I did?
I’m sorry.
Somehow, I haven’t been feeling very good lately.
Could you ask me fewer questions today?
Either that, or can we just not talk quite so much?
You’re tired, Sensei. Maybe you should sleep a little.
Tired? I guess I look that way. You’re right. I must look that way.
I feel bad for you Touko-san.
You can’t do your own research because you’re busy with miscellaneous tasks.
I’m not doing any miscellaneous tasks!
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry for raising my voice like that.
You must be shocked.
Did something happen? Touko-san?
No, nothing.
You’re busy with miscellaneous tasks and can’t do your own research. Does that bother you?
How do you know about... ?
I found the homepage for this research center.
I saw the list of researchers and published dissertations, but I couldn't find you.
That’s right. I haven’t published any dissertations since I came here. But I mean to very soon.
You’re okay now. You have time for your own research now?
What are you saying? What do you mean, Lain?
I’m not a research subject, am I?
That’s why I’m not useful to you.
We can end now if you’d like.
I can’t see them anymore.
I’m wasting your time.
Lain.
You’re like a sister to me.
I’m the one who said that we could just talk.
I don’t think of you as a nuisance.
And...
There’s nothing for you to worry about, Touko-san. It was a suicide.
How do you know about that?
I read it in the paper. It was on the bulletin board here, too.
I see. You’re right.
What kind of research do you do?
As I said before, I’m trying to develop a new treatment system using my background as a counselor and psychiatrist.
But it looks like I’m failing as a counselor and a psychiatrist right now.
Why?
I think I’m becoming mentally unstable, now. Just a few moments ago, I...I’m sorry.
Touko-san... are you okay?