Hello, Touko-san.
Hello, Lain.
Okay, from today we’re going to really tackle what’s bothering you, Lain-chan.
I’m sorry.
I mean Lain.
We’re going to try to figure things out so you don’t see nightmares anymore.
I haven't seen nightmares much lately. Sometimes I hear things, though.
Hear things? Like what?
I don’t know.
It sounds like someone talking.
I don’t like hearing it, so I try my best to ignore it.
Hmm. Do you know whose voice you hear?
I don’t know. It can be a man’s voice or a woman’s voice.
Where do the voices seem to come from?
From the sky.
The sky? From what part of the sky?
From the electric lines. Somehow...
The electric lines... Do you know what’s inside of electric lines?
Wiring that carries electricity.
Right. They carry electricity that comes from power plants. Do feel like you sense electricity?
I don't really know. Sometimes it seems to come from the sky; not the electric lines.
Are you bothered by it right now?
No. I’m not scared now. But...
When you told your mother, did she tell you not to tell anyone else about these things?
Uh-huh.
People who don’t hear these things would think strange things about you if you told them, huh?
You don’t have to worry about telling me anything you want to.
You don’t have to worry, okay?
I’m not going to think strange things about you.
Because I’m sick?
No, Lain. Let’s see. You know about "sleep paralysis"?
Is it when a demon comes out and you can’t move your body?
Right. Have you ever had that happen to you?
Many times.
It was frightening, wasn’t it?
Uh, huh.
Do you know why sleep paralysis happens?
Why?
The human body is very mysterious.
When you’re sleeping, there are times when your mind is awake, and times when your body is awake.
Do you understand?
Sort of...
Well, that’s good enough for now. What parts of you are awake right now?
Both?
Hmm.
Suppose I said something really scary right now, and you felt scared enough to run out of this room.
What would you do?
Run out of the room.
Okay.
Suppose that you feel so scared that you want to run out of this room, but your body is asleep and you can’t move.
That's what sleep paralysis is.
So if you’re having a nightmare but your body is asleep and you can’t move, you are having sleep paralysis.
You see?
If you know what’s involved, it’s not so scary, is it?
No. It isn’t.