Let’s skip counseling today and just relax instead.
You came all the way out here.
Do you want something to drink?
I cried so much that I’m thirsty.
Touko-san, I’ll start keeping my diary. Honestly, this time.
Don’t force yourself. You’re a kind girl.
I’m not forcing myself.
The diary is for me, after all.
And the next time I hear the voices, I’ll listen to see what they are saying.
Then, I’ll tell you what they said, Touko-san.
Thank you, Lain.
Happy birthday, by the way, Touko-san.
Huh! My birthday?
I made this for you with my mom.
Really? I’m so happy! Can I open it?
Sure.
Cookies! Good timing. We were actually out of teacakes. Let's have them together.
Is it good?
Mmm. It tastes like tea.
You said that you like tea, so we made the cookies that way.
Thank you. But then we better have a different kind of tea.
It won’t go with black tea?
No, not that it wouldn’t go with it, but it would be too bad if we couldn’t enjoy the tea and cookies as much as possible.
Should I have made cookies with a different flavor?
Oh, no, no.
Not at all!
But you took all the trouble to make such nice cookies, and I want to enjoy them as much as possible.
That’s all.
Really?
Really. Thanks so much, Lain.
Sensei, it hurts.