Hello, Lain.
(in a soft voice) Hello.
Hmm.
You don’t sound so energetic.
Maybe you don’t feel up for this.
Why don’t we quit now?
Okay?
But since you came all the way out here, how about a cup of tea or something?
What would you like?
Don’t be shy.
I wanna do it.
You don’t have to force yourself. That might make you feel even worse. Take my word for it.
I want to be cured.
Cured... But you’re not sick, Lain.
But this is a hospital, isn’t it?
Well, this place can function as a hospital, but I see patients at my research room as well.
Right now, I don’t know if you are really sick or not.
My hunch is that you are probably not sick, Lain.
Still, if you aren’t feeling well or are worried about something, I’d like to be able to help you.
I’m not sick?
Right now, I’m not completely sure, but you’re probably just fine.
Even if you are sick, I’ll make sure that you are cured.
You’re absolutely sure you can cure me?
Absolutely. I will not let you be sick.
Sensei, why are you so kind to me? Is it because it is your job?
Hmm... You’re right that this is a part of my work.
But it’s a type of work that’s hard to see as just work.
Most of the time, I see patients, diagnose them as objectively as possible, and give them psychological treatment, but it isn’t enough to make them better.
I’m a researcher as well as a doctor.
If I see someone suffering, I must try and help that person.
I want to do everything I can to help that person.
You would do that for anybody?
To be specific, if I see someone suffering from something for which the cause is physical and obvious, I refer that person to a specialist.
If there is a car accident or a poisoning, that's what I would do.
To put it simply, I’m not the kind of doctor who treats people who have something wrong with them physically.
So I have...
I can’t tell for sure without doing a close examination, but I know that you had an examination before you came here and that no problems were found.
And just by talking to you here, Lain, you don’t seem to have anything wrong with you at all.
But you need to talk to me and tell me much more about what’s going on with you, or I can’t really help you with what’s bothering you.