Hello, Lain.
I write in my diary everyday. Sometimes I don’t have much to write, though.
Don’t worry about it.
If you force yourself, you’ll just want to give up.
I don't know how many diaries I've had that I couldn't stick to for long.
Have you seen any of them since then?
I’ve been okay.
Really? That’s good. There’s something I want to confirm with you today.
What?
You have really good eyesight, don’t you, Lain?
Really good?
You’ve had eye exams at school, haven’t you? What’s your score?
One-point-five.
Your eyesight is really even better than that, isn’t it?
But I wanted to have the same score as all the other kids.
Well, there’s no point having the examination, then.
At the last hospital you used to go to, they examined your eyes, too.
But they did it differently than at your school.
They had a machine that measures eyesight automatically.
The machine only measures as far as three-point-zero, and your score was three-point-zero.
Kids with such good eyesight are extremely rare, so...
The doctor in charge of your eye-exam spoke with a cancer specialist, who said he saw no problems.
Oh.
Lain, what can you see outside the window?
Trees and a gate to the research center in the distance.
And beyond that?
Buildings.
Mountains.
And beyond that?
I can’t see anything further.
Nothing at all?
A purplish color that looks like a curtain.
Thank you.
I’m sorry to pepper you with all these questions.
I think that you probably see the world in a different way than I do.
Lain, don’t look so glum.
It’s nothing to worry about.
It’s not such a bad thing... I’m sorry for saying that.
I guess it is bad thing for you.
To see things so differently.
I don’t know.
But I had a feeling that I’m probably different from everybody else.
I feel like I’m the only person who can hear and see some things.
It makes me very uncomfortable.
I think that I will be disliked.
Is that the reason?
It might be. I think that you’d have to be seen by a specialist.
No. I want to see you. I don’t want to see any of the other doctors here. They all scare me.
Why don’t we just keep this as a secret?
A secret?
Uh huh. It will be our secret until you aren’t worried about it anymore.
Is that okay?
I’m your big sister, remember? I’m not going to take you anywhere that you will be scared.
Touko-san.