By "what's bothering me", you mean... my nightmares? Me seeing strange things? Feeling like someone is touching me when no one is there?
Aren't those symptoms of schizophrenia?
Schizophrenia? Where did you hear a word like that? Who said that to you?
I looked it up in a book.
Lain, it’s a good things to study hard, but it’s dangerous to go digging around and diagnosing yourself when you aren’t sick.
Have you heard the expression "Sickness and health starts with the mind?"
Actually, I haven’t.
Oh?
Anyway, if you start diagnosing yourself, you’re going to start believing that you have all sorts of things wrong with you.
I just wanted to know... what's going on with me.
I see.
I understand.
I think your intentions are right.
But I’d like to ask something of you.
Please don’t go around prying… investigating, for things that you think are wrong with you.
Can I ask that of you?
Then will you help me find what’s wrong?
Of course I will.
So let’s make a promise.
I will tell you everything I understand about you.
I won’t hide anything from you.
If you lie can I cut off your finger?
Hmm... you can do something even worse. You can hammer a nail into my head.
You’re goofy, Sensei.
Seriously, though, I really want to help you.
I’m an only child, and I always wished I had a younger sister—someone like you, Lain.
You’re my big sister then?
I’d be happy if you saw me that way.
I will.
Thank you. Anyway, let’s end for today. You’re tired, aren’t you?
Not at all! But I’ll do what you asked me to do, Sensei.
Now that's the spirit! ...Oh dear. Looks like I'm the one who's tired here after all.
You’re tired of me?
Not at all!
I’ve just had a lot of other work to do today.
I like you and I’ll miss you until we meet again, Lain.
That makes me feel better.
Let’s end now, then. It’s getting late and we don’t want your mother to worry.
Goodbye, Touko-sensei.
Goodbye, Lain-chan.
Just call me Lain. It’s a bit weird for a "big sister" to call me Lain-chan.
Okay then, goodbye, Lain.
Goodbye.