The ego is your sense of who you are, isn’t it?
Yes, but more technically phrased, the ego is a part of the mind you use to experience as yourself and to recognize yourself.
Do you get it?
Not at all.
Okay, so you have an idea that you are Lain.
In such the structural element, the "EGO" is right there.
Linguistically, "myself" describes all of you, right?
"Ego" is, however, one of the parts of your mind you use to recognize that all of experiences I have had were mine.
Saying "it’s just to realize that you are yourself" is somewhat better to understand?
I can get the last part, but it is still beyond my understanding.
I like your honesty.
So the girl, Lain, has various emotions, such as kindness, loneliness and things like that.
Now the EGO is what is left when you don’t feel any emotions.
I guess I understand a little...
For example, the Lain who woke up this morning and what Lain is now here are the same, right?
Right.
What Lain will be tomorrow should be the same as those.
I guess so.
I mean if your ego works properly, you can recognize that you exist continuously and confirm that that existence is "myself." If your ego doesn’t work properly...
If it doesn’t?
We call such a situation "identity disorder" in the medical field.
On the other hand, there is also an "isolation disorder" which means you think that you are not yourself.
He, he, they sound like bad diseases, don’t they?
Yet anyone your age usually doesn’t complete his or her ego until later.
You just can gradually recognize yourself with age.
So is it wrong to think that I understand myself at my age?
It just happens to be that such things happen all the time.