You don’t want to do anything? How about your research?
No one will want to read my paper anyway.
What’s wrong? It’s not like you to play a victim.
Not like me! What am I?
You’re just Touko-san, Touko-san.
I’ve been severed from society. I’m no longer connected.
That’s not true. I’m connected to you. I’m connected to society. That’s why you’re connected, too.
Something’s wrong with me, isn’t there?
The times when I talk to you and the time I spend with everything else are separate.
From your point of view, my life must be a contradiction.
My point of view?
From your point of view, this world doesn’t exist.
No. That’s not true. I’m connected to this world.
I can’t take it anymore.
I can’t even stand this moment.
That’s not all.
My memories of tomorrow...the memories I’ll have in the future are in disarray.
Is this a delusion caused by worrying?
Am I experiencing something I shouldn’t be experiencing?
That’s you, isn’t it?
It is me! Because it is me!
Wouldn’t you be better off if you were just being yourself?
I can’t understand my sense of self from moment to moment!
The judgment you have exactly at that moment is you, Touko-san. The rest is...
The rest is...
Ordinary data.