I’m sorry about last time... but I’m relieved.
I was worried that you didn’t like me and wouldn't come anymore.
...I’m sorry.
There’s no reason to apologize.
I was the one who asked you a bad question.
Can you forgive me?
...thank you.
So I thought we could talk about what we see on these pictures today.
They had that at the last hospital.
Really? I wanted to play with this.
That's some kind of test, isn't it?
Amazing Lain! Do you know about it?
They call this a Rorschach test.
This isn’t really a test.
Think of it as a game.
But that’s boring.
Hmm... I guess so.
If you think it's boring, we'll stop the test.
How’s that?
Okay.
Okay. What do you see?
A splotch.
Um, right.
But does it look like anything?
What do you see?
Me? Hmm... a person’s face, I think.
Is it angry? Is it also crying?
It looks a little angry.
This is boring.
Lain...
Right. A promise is a promise. Let’s stop.