Lain, I’d like for you to tell me the truth.
The truth?
You don’t have any friend named Misato-chan, do you?
Ha, ha. What do you mean? That’s silly of you.
I asked Kyoko-chan.
And?
She said that there is no Misato-chan. She said, "aren't you confusing it with Minako?"
Is that what you believe?
I’m not accusing you, but this is very important.
For you to write your report?
I won’t deny that. But I’m concerned about you personally.
About me personally?
Yes.
I’m concerned that you might be creating imaginary friends and running away into your own little world.
That is a sickness.
You said that kids often have that, and that there’s nothing wrong with it, Touko-san.
Misato-chan isn't an imaginary friend, either.
Then where is she? Can you call her right now? Can you give her a call right now, in front of me?
She can’t be contacted. She moved away.
Can you do anything to prove to me that she exists?
That she exists?
Yes. Can you prove that?
My memory...
Look, Lain, I want to believe you, but I can’t read your mind or tell what your memories are.