I’m sorry about last session, Lain. I don’t know myself why I became so angry.
It’s okay, Touko-san.
It’s just that aside from this issue with Misato-chan, I can’t see anything wrong with you.
We’ll have to work on it slowly.
Will you finish your paper in time?
I’m not putting anything about you in my paper.
I’ll use information from other clients.
It’s not your problem anyway, Lain.
You’re gentle, Lain.
I’m not gentle.
I have to apologize.
I should have apologized right away, but I’ve done some things behind your back.
I lied and told some of your friends that I’m a private tutor.
I asked your friends about you.
I needed the information for my report.
I should have these things with more benevolent intentions, but... are you angry?
I’m sorry, Lain.
But I did it for y... No, I didn’t do it for you.
I did it for my work.