Good morning, Touko-san.
Good morning. How are you? Have you been feeling healthy?
Uh huh. I thought about the things you talked about last month and I’ve somehow been feeling better.
Oh, that’s great.
Actually, though, it’s against the rules to talk about the things we talked about last month.
There were cases where people had something irreversible trigger from speculating too much.
Irreversible?
Their sickness could worsen, and sometimes, patients can hurt themselves physically.
Suicide?
Well, that would be the worst-case scenario.
I don’t want to die.
Of course not!
Far from it.
But when people become troubled emotionally, they start to see things and act differently than you or I would.
See things differently?
They can lose their fear of dying or hurting themselves.
In fact they start to feel that dying or getting hurt are very good things.
You can’t understand that, can you?
I am afraid of those things.
Sure! Me too. We’re the same way. That’s normal.
Ok.