I’m sorry ma’am.
I can handle it from here.
(pause) Lain, I’m sorry.
I thought that if I didn't do this, your would never see me again.
I just wanted to apologize.
I think I was arrogant about my assumptions about you.
Still, I wanted you to understand and to be comfortable.
I just thought that if you could face your dreams and understand where they were coming from, that they would stop.
I’m sorry, Touko-san.
Why?
I lied to you... I didn’t keep the diary.
That’s okay. I told you that it was all up to you.
You were trying to be helpful to me.
Thank you. I’m grateful that you feel that way. Can you forgive me, Lain?
Yes.
I’m so glad.
I was so sad when you walked away from our session.
I cried.
I felt so bad.
I though you didn’t like me anymore.
Touko-san, don’t cry.
Oh... It’s so silly of me to cry over this. I’m sorry, Lain.
Don’t cry.
These are tears of joy, Lain. I’m so glad.
Joy?
Yes. Tears of joy.
I’m really happy, too. I feel so close to you.