You know about neurosis? Wow, Lain. You’re going to have to start counseling me.
I know the word, not its meaning.
What kind of image?
The mind changes and becomes distorted?
Yes. You’ve got the general idea.
That’s awful. You won’t teach me anymore?
No.
I’m really telling you that you got the general idea.
Neurosis is a state in which there is nothing wrong with a person physically, yet the person has irrational fears and perceives threats.
This places a lot of stress on the person and makes her feel sick.
It’s only inside of their heads?
We used to think so.
But after a lot of research, we think that an imbalance of the autonomic nerves in the brain is related to it.
What I mean is, something is wrong in the body, too.
We used to categorize physical symptoms as psychosomatic.
But we’ve been finding more and more that conditions we thought were only of the mind involve the body itself.
Psychosomatic?
Oh, Lain, if you ask so many questions, your head is going to explode!
You’ve heard about people who lose a lot of weight because of stress, or go bald?
That’s psychosomatic.
Lain, you don’t, by any chance...
No, I don’t have that kind of problem.
Oh, I’m relieved. That was hasty of me!