It’s not a memory. It’s a record.
Well, they’re vaguely similar. But it’s no time to be playing word-games.
You would understand if you were connected.
Connected to what?
Lain, you say that Misato-chan exists, but you are the only person who says so.
How can you expect anyone else to understand?
There is something wrong with this.
How can anyone believe you?
You don't believe me, Touko-san?
Unfortunately, no.
But that’s because I’ve looked very closely into this personally, and all the facts point against it.
If you could show me some objective proof that that I am mistaken, that would be different.
How would I prove that she exists?
How?
Well show me other people who’ve known her.
Show me her identification or birth certificate or something.
More than anything else, show me that she’s a human being that exists and walks around in a human body.
She doesn’t exist if she doesn’t have a human body?
Of course not! She’s not a ghost, is she?
Professor Takashima didn’t exist, then?
But he did exist.
He had a body before he died.
He lived and walked around in a human body.
There is ample evidence that he existed.
Many people who are alive now knew him.
There are records of his existence.
Let’s cool it, Lain.
I’m not here to have a question and answer session with you.
I’m here to treat you.
I do not acknowledge Misato-chan’s existence.