I wanted to ask last time, but why do have that kind of hairstyle?
It’s weird?
No, it’s great! You really look good that way. Is it a popular look at your school?
No. It’s just my own style.
You mentioned that you want to be like other kids. Why do you have a unique look?
It comes from the right, and probably, that’s why it goes out of the left. That’s why...
It works a little bit like a magic charm, then. I used have a magic charm, too.
You did, Touko-san?
Sure.
It didn’t have to do with hairstyle, but I used to have a lucky rabbit’s foot.
I used to believe that it would keep me safe and happy, and I tied it to my backpack.
Looking back, it seems so ghastly.
To tie a little bunny’s foot to my backpack.
But then again, believing in the rabbit’s foot really made me feel safer.
A magic charm?
Yeah.
Your hair looks really good, though, Lain.
If you had a hairstyle like everyone else’s, it wouldn’t be like you.
I think you look great the way you are.