So, how’s school?
Normal.
What do you mean by normal? Not interesting, not boring, just normal?
Yes...
How about friends?
I have friends.
Do you often play with them?
Yes, but everyone’s busy with cram school. The only place I go is here...
Don’t you want to learn something? Calligraphy, or take swimming lesso... ooohhh...
It’s okay; don’t worry about it.
I’m sorry... I'm far from a good counselor.
I’d rather stay at home than go out and do something.
What do you do at home?
That’s a secret.
Aw, that’s mean. You won’t tell me.
But I’m ashamed.
Are you doing things you’re ashamed of?
Maybe...
Now I want to know! Ah, so be it... But I’d really like to know...
Do I have to tell you?
I’d be glad if you did tell me.
I talk to my stuffed animals.
Ha, ha, is that it? That’s completely normal. And here I thought...
Thought what?
Ha, ha, never mind! I used to have a stuffed animal I loved...
What kind of stuffed animal?
A dragon I got at the bank. Weird, huh?
Why is that weird?
Well, aren’t girls supposed to play with cute stuffed animals?
It wasn’t even a stuffed animal... it was a piggy bank dragon.
But I still treasured it.
I called it Tacchan and talked to it all the time.
Me too. I talk to my animals. Is that normal?
That’s normal! Do I look weird to you?
No...
You’re the same as me, Lain, we’re not weird at all!