Have you seen or heard anything since then?
No.
See!
It was a state of mind, Lain.
I think that you probably won’t see them again, but if you do, don’t get discouraged.
You’ll get over it gradually.
I won’t get better right away?
Hmm. I don’t know. How old were you when you started having problems with them?
I was eleven.
So it’s been over a year now. During that time, how often did it happen?
I don’t remember... many times.
Sometimes, even if there doesn't seem to be an explanation for it immediately, these things may go away.
But if you decide that they’ve gone away completely and become complacent, there’s a chance that they may come back.
I can’t say for certain that that will happen with you, but even if you don’t see them for a while, I’d like you to continue what you’ve been doing up till now.
Do you want to stop coming here, Lain?
No. I like seeing you.
Thank you.
I guess that there’s no problem, then.
You’re doing well, but you’ll promise me that you will keep coming here?
Yes. In exchange, I want you to teach me some things.
Why?
For homework?
Sure.
You won’t believe it, but I was pretty sharp in junior high school.
Ha, ha.
Learning to read and write was tough, though.
I don’t mean that. I want to know more about your work. Is that okay?
Hmm.
I don't think it’s a very good idea, but if you’re really curious, okay. Learning about things that make you curious is a great way to study.
But you have to make time for your schoolwork, too.
I’ll promise to teach you about my work if you promise to do your schoolwork.
Can you promise me that?
Yes, I promise.
And if you break your promise...
I’ll whack you with a blowfish!