You’re really yearning all the time, aren’t you, Lain?
Probably...
I’m envious.
Human perception is a wild thing.
If you start feeling something, you start believing it.
I don't know how to explain to anyone that I am really me.
But being able to question that sense of self is a special talent.
I don’t want a talent like that.
Yeah.
I’m sure you feel really strongly that way right now.
But I feel that it can be a good thing for you, too.
I don't understand it well right now, but I think that if you can include and accept that as part of yourself, it would help you in the long run.
I won’t change?
I don’t know.
You might change naturally and stop having nightmares.
If that happens, you’d be like most other kids.
But I won’t know if I’ve gotten better. I might have nightmares again.
Yeah. But things will change from now on.
What do you mean?
I mean that you’re not alone. I’m here, and you can talk to me about things.
That’s true, Touko-san.