Are you happy at your school?
Yes, I am!
What makes you so happy!
You know, playing and talking with my best friend.
That’s good! It is a good thing to like school, isn’t it?
Were you happy?
Not really, because I didn’t have many friends there.
You feel sad without friends at school.
Yeah... I’m sorry
About what?
That story reminds you of a bad memory.
Well, it certainly wasn’t good memory, but that’s okay.
I actually feel sorry for my past, but my current job makes me think that was a good experience for me.
Good experience?
Yes.
For example, such an experience is sometimes so useful to analyze the psychology of those who doesn’t want to go to school.
It sounds difficult.
I’m sorry, I’m talking about myself now! Whenever I talk about my job, I tend to get lost in it.
I guess I would make a better patient.
Okay, let’s change the subject. Well, what is your best friend like?
She is really cheerful and nice to me. I’m really happy around her.
What's her name?
Misato.
Okay... Misato. What do you usually do together?
We read books together at her place and I listen to her playing violin sometimes.
Wow, she can play the violin.
Awesome!
She must be a good friend.
Why don’t you come over with her next time?
But she is so shy.
So shy?
Maybe... I’ll ask her anyway. I’m guessing she wouldn’t want to.
Well, I wish she could.