Are you troubled about anything?
No, I’m not. How about you, Touko-san?
Sometimes. I feel like something bad might happen.
You’re feeling delusional?
Yes, but unlike with you, it isn’t a strange delusional problem with perception.
I wonder if that’s true.
But how about the feelings you have about that man?
Aren’t those feelings delusional?
Who is "that man"?
The man you’re thinking about right now.
You can tell what I’m thinking.
Wow!
You have super powers?
Is that why you poke fun at me sometimes?
But I’m connected to you, Touko-san.
"Connected"? In what way?
It probably wouldn’t make sense if I tried to explain it to you.
That’s called psychosis, Lain.
Believing yourself to be a unique "chosen" person or that you are God.
That’s a serious disease.
I’m sick. How about you?
I’m not sick. I’m...