I’m sorry. I just was trying to explain this issue to you.
I like you too Lain, though I’m not sure why.
I suppose I just enjoy talking to you. That’s it.
It’s probably just because I like my job!
I just thought it had to do with you, but I guess not.
It is enough for me to be able to understand my feelings.
I can never read your mind, so I can never know that you like me as much as I like you.
Sounds lonely...
I’m sorry, but you know, this is one of the ways for me to know that.
I’m so happy with you saying that you like me.
Are you happy with me saying I like you?
Yes, indeed.
Yes, that is enough. Lain, I like you.
But still, as you can never comprehend all of me, it is impossible for me to know everything about you.
If we could know everything about each other, I could be you and vice versa.
I mean you do not have to be Lain unless we are different people.
I really like Lain even though Lain is hard to understand sometimes.
You like the mysterious Lain?
Well, I like Lain who I don’t know very well. Of course, that is not all I like.
I want to know everything about you!!
So do I! But it’s impossible.
Impossible?
Yes. That is because even I don’t know who I am!
Well, I don’t know how to explain this to you. Lain is Lain and I am me.
Actually it might be still impossible even if we became the same person.
The same person?
Yes, Lain and I are exactly the same!
We see the same things, have the same ideas and take same actions.
Everything.
Even our looks are the same!
In this situation, there is only an identity that you KEEP, isn't there?
Yet even if such an identification is gone.
If you thought "Here is Lain," then I cannot exist there.
The same thing can happen to you!
That is why it’s impossible to understand each other at the same time.
But what if you would answer every question I ask.
Still, it would be impossible?
Right, but they are not all possible questions, are they?
I need time to answer those questions and those answers could be changed eventually, such as I used to think one thing, but now I have changed my mind — something like that.
It's impossible after all, isn’t it?
Yes, I wish I could go inside your mind and answer everything you want to know...