Touko-san.
Good morning.
I’m sorry.
I stayed up all night preparing my paper.
Everything is scattered everywhere.
Could you give me a second?
Maybe I should go home?
It’s all right. Don’t worry. Oh, shoot, I’m out of tea.
I can go buy you some.
Thanks.
But please don’t. I appreciate your feelings.
Have a seat, Lain.
I thought that maybe I ought to take a break, too.
Are you very busy?
A little.
After that thing happened to Professor Takashima.
Now I have to do a lot of his work, too.
I’ve had a lot of new clients, to boot.
Can you do your research?
Lain, don’t mind that stuff too much.
It’ll be tough for a while, but I have things to do.
For now, I’m just happy just concentrating on my work.
You aren’t sad?
You’ll understand one day Lain. It’s a wonderful thing to have work that’s fulfilling.
I don’t think I would understand. Instead of something like that...
Instead of... what do you mean? Did you do something fun lately?
Yes. I think everything is going to work out well.
What will work out well?
Things about me.