What is university like?
You’re in junior high school now, aren’t you, Lain?
So if you’re in junior high and want to keep studying, you go to high school, right?
University is where people go if they want to keep studying after high school.
Do you like to study, Sensei?
I didn’t used to.
But I went to America as an exchange student when I was in junior high school, and I started to feel differently then.
You were an exchange student. Wow!
At the time, I just went because my parents wanted me to.
But people have different ways of seeing things in other countries, and I learned a lot from that.
Looking back, it was a lot of work, and I was very nervous at first, but now I’m really grateful that I was able to be an exchange student.
I learned English, too.
That’s amazing, Touko-sensei!
Oh, it’s not so amazing.
There are lots of people who have studied much more than I have.
No matter how you put it, I'm a really lazy person
I liked to fool around, really.
It’s boring to just study, isn’t it?
Do you like to study, Lain?
Not really.
What subjects don’t you like?
Japanese and physical education.
I see. So you don’t like exercise.
No, I don’t like physical education.
You like exercise, then?
Yes.
What kind of exercise do you like?
The metal beam.
Wow!
I used to like running, but I was never good at the metal beam.
I would spin around and get too dizzy.
I like to spin around.
Both frontwards and backwards?
Yes, both.
What don’t you like?
You don’t have to answer if you don’t want to.
But, what kind of study do you like?
I'm sorry.
Are you tired?
Why don't we end early today?