A rumor?
Does it bother you?
Someone is spreading rumors about you?
Is that a delusion of persecution?
Some other kind of delusion?
Well, it might just be a lack of self-confidence.
Why do you have so much confidence, even when you’re sick, Lain?
I’m sick. What’s the name of my disease? Schizophrenia? Manic depression? Something else?
You aren’t any of those things.
You have pathomimesis.
That’s what you call the imitation of disease.
Then I’m not really sick?
You don’t exist.
I just think that you’re here.
Everyone has been tricked.
We’ve all been shown some glimpse of your existence.
That’s why no one really remembers you.
It’s not like you to be mad. Some of us don’t seem to exist, though. Which are you?
I think that you think I’m here.
You’re a delusion that created a delusion.
All these things, your constructed diseases and your voices, are delusions.
How about me? Am I here?
That’s why I have to heal you!
You’re so serious. But you’re an elite. You’ve been chosen.
That’s right.
I’m trying hard to be here.
I would rather have been out playing and fooling around, but I’ve gone to school and studied and worked hard to get here.
I feel sorry for you, Touko-san.