You don’t have much energy.
I’m tired.
Are you tired of doing miscellaneous chores?
Is someone having you do waste your time with small tasks?
Yeah. I do feel that way sometimes.
Do you think you have some kind of psychological condition?
Do you think you might have caught something from me?
Ha, ha.
Why do you think I’m like this? I know and understand the things I am talking about.
You’re okay, Touko-san. You’ll be better by tomorrow.
I’ll be "better"?
You’ll be in a world where you don’t suffer.
Am I myself when I am by myself or when I’m with you?
You’re always yourself. Even when you doubt my existence.
I doubt your existence?
Yes. You don’t want to believe that I exist.
Why would I have a problem like that because I treat you?
There is information you wouldn’t understand now. You aren’t doing well psychologically.
"Information I wouldn’t understand now?" But I want to know now.
Yes. But it would be too difficult for you to understand now.
You’re thinking about what’s best for me, aren’t you, Lain?
Of course, I am. I like you.