So... Ms. Iwakura, please wait there in the waiting room.
Lain, you don’t have to worry so much.
Please sit down there.
Ah... do you want some juice or something else to drink?
It's fine if you don't want any. Don't worry.
Let's see...
I'm thirsty, so I'm going for tea... Would you mind joining me?
Because it will look funny if only I drink it.
Thank you.
Which one do you want?
We have many to choose from.
The same as you.
Black tea?
Got it.
Just a moment...
You can put the sugar and milk in it if you want.
Here you go.
Not bad, huh?
Earl Grey tea, I really love it.
Earl Grey?
Right.
Even with tea there are lots of kinds, with different smells and tastes.
Does it taste good?
Well...
It suits my taste.
But I'm not sure about you, Lain.
If you want to, you can drink a little bit.
If it’s not to your taste, I can make something else for you.
Here...