How are you feeling, Lain?
I’m doing okay. How about you, Touko-san?
Pretty much as always. I could use a little more time to calm down and think things over, though.
You’re very busy?
Yes... Ha, ha. Now our roles are reversed. I feel like you are counseling me.
Ha, ha.
Ha, ha. By the way, what did you decide to do about the diary?
I decided to keep a diary.
Wow, that’s great! I didn’t waste my money right before payday.
I’ll pay you for the diary.
I’m joking, I’m joking.
But I get paid well anyway.
But I guess it's too low considering how many hours I work a day.
Oh, no.
This isn’t good.
I'm just grumbling about myself.
But you’re funny, Sensei. You’re a lot of fun.
Ha, ha.
Well, why don’t we begin?
Let’s pick up where we left off last time.
Have you learned the word "ego" at school?
Uh-huh. I looked into it. It’s about knowing that you are yourself?
Right.
People around your age can get unsure about that.
They ask themselves "what kind of person am I?" Boys sometimes think that they are heroes and that they will accomplish some superhuman feat someday.
Girls sometimes imagine that they don't belong with their own families.
They think instead that they are members of a rich elite family, and that a prince on a white steed will surely come one day to take them away.
I don’t feel that way. I think that I’m just me.
But It’s hard to tell what you are just by yourself, isn’t it?
When I was younger, I thought that there was a different me, and that somehow I wasn't the person I was at the time.
A different me?
Yes.
For example, if there was something happening that I didn’t like, I wondered why I had to be the one dealing with it.
I thought there had to be some kind of mistake.
I thought that someday I would return to the real me.
I also thought things like, if there was a big earthquake, everyone would die, but I would be the only survivor.
I thought that I was someone special; someone "chosen." In another words, I believed in a "me" that could not be.
It’s funny, isn’t it?
I don’t believe that I’m anyone chosen. I’m okay with being ordinary.