Who decides the names of diseases?
Various doctors.
But we have general criterions.
We have the ICD and the DSM, which are international standards for the definition of mental diseases.
We know that if a person has a certain set of symptoms, we can consult these standards and find the exact name of the disease the person is suffering from.
As you know, the mind can be a difficult thing to understand.
For that reason, psychiatrists have publications, and we communicate all the time, sharing our data and our understanding of mental illness.
We accumulate data and categorize it so that we can diagnose patients as correctly as possible.
There’s mental illness you don't understand? Not even you?
To tell you the truth, we don’t understand much of this at all.
If there has been a successful treatment method for a patient with a certain disease in the past, we can apply that treatment method toward a patient suffering from the same disease in the present.
Much of this has to do with experience.
You do this even if you don’t know if a person can be cured?
Right.
You can’t tell if a person will be cured.
We can only try our best to heal and help with our experience from the past.
That’s usually the case.
But from the point of view of the patient, knowing if one will become better is very important.
In fact, the understanding of the mechanisms behind getting better is an area of study of its own.
I see. It would be so much better if we could understand everything.