You seem to be busy lately, Touko-san.
Yes.
The deadline for my paper is coming up, and although I’ve been waiting for a long time for someone to relieve me with some of my work, it hasn’t happened.
That means more work for me.
Sure, it’s a little hard.
Is it tiresome?
I’m okay, Lain. You don’t have to worry about it.
I’m worried about you, Touko-san.
About me? Well thank you. I appreciate your feelings.
Will you continue to like me, Touko-san?
Of course! You’re my little sister, remember? I don’t have any reasons not to like you.
But I made you mad.
That’s true.
But that was just because you’re growing intellectually, we were having a discussion and we had a difference of opinion.
But let’s leave that alone.
There’s no reason for me to dislike you because we had a difference of opinion.
Do you have important people in your life aside from me?
Sure.
I have friends, too.
You have people in your life that are important to you aside from me, don’t you?
I do. But if I had to choose one person, I would choose you.
That makes me happy. Then, I’ll pick you, too.
Really? But is that okay? What about the other important people in your life?
If you chose me and I didn’t choose you, won’t you feel sad? I don’t want you to feel sad.
Won’t your lover be sad?
Huh? Um, well, yes. Are you interested in my private life, Lain?
I want to know about you.
Things having to do about my lover are a secret. You’re a bit young for that kind of thing, anyway.
Too young?
You may eventually have a love life of your own. But love is a pretty complicated thing.
Complicated?
Yes.
I have by doubts and worries about it, too.
I’m human.
I make mistakes and have regrets.
Even now I have feelings that I can’t figure out.
See?
It’s complicated.
Complicated...