It’s because I’m weird...
Wait a second Lain.
You’re not a weird kid at all.
If you're a kid with an active imagination, you're gonna have that kind of experience where you see human eyes in the patterns of a wooden ceiling.
But that's not the case.
Do you dislike being different from others?
I’m not sure.
Okay.
Lain is Lain because she is different.
You have a very strong imagination, and that’s a good thing.
So don’t say that you're weird.
I don’t think that at all.
But... the test...
I’m sorry, but... yeah, you’re troubled, right?
I want to make sure you're not troubled.
In order to help you, I have to know more about you.
I don’t want you to do anything you dislike.
I'll do anything I can to help you solve your problems. You're the only one who can truly understand yourself right?
Nobody can understand Lain except Lain, right?
Only you can solve your own problems.
For me to be able to help you, I need your cooperation.
What should I do?
Right now you don't need to do anything.
Since you and I are friends, if we keep talking, I’ll slowly start to understand more and more about you.
Then, sometimes I'll say "You might want to try this." and if you think "That sounds nice, okay.", let's try it out...
So right now, it’d be best if you tell me all about yourself.
You won’t tell anyone?
Nope, it’ll be our secret.
Not even my friends, or my mother?
I promise. If I lie, one thousand needles!
One thousand needles?
Don’t kids your age know that?
When I was a kid, whenever we made a promise, we said, "If I break the promise, I will drink 1000 needles."
Wouldn’t that hurt?
A lot!... Right! How many needles are in my stomach right now? Miss Iwakura? ...I was made to drink them 5 times.
...five thousand?
Wrong! Yesterday, since I went to the bathroom and flushed everything out, there’s zero!
Sensei, that's gross!...