There are many people who have had experienced sleep paralysis, but we don’t call them "sick."
But...
Hmm... there might be only a few people who have experienced what you have.
Still, I don’t think you should be called "sick" just because of your experiences.
A lot of things can happen to a person while she’s young and impressionable.
But I’m scared and I hate this.
What's so scary about your dream?
I start to feel that I don't belong. Like I am an unneeded thing.
You "don't belong"?
I feel that I am being told to come back because I’m unneeded.
Come back? Come back where?
To myself.
Hmm. This is hard to understand. You want you to come back to yourself?
I don’t know. But it feels as if there was another myself, touching my body, ripping it apart
(interrupting) And it’s painful?
It isn’t painful, but it’s frightening.
I see. Does this happen when you’re asleep?
Probably.
Probably? This happens sometimes when you’re not dreaming?
I don't know.
Sometimes it happens when I’m all by myself, and sometimes when I’m talking to my friends.
Tell me what happens when you’re not alone. This happens when you’re just having conversations?
Yes. While I’m just talking, it suddenly...
How do you notice it? Do your friends call out to you?
Suddenly...
Is there something that triggers it?
I was afraid, and I felt better after staying motionless for a while.
Can you explain what it felt like, or what you saw? Could you draw a picture?
No, I can’t.
I see... Oh!
We have to end.
I’m sorry, Lain.
I have to go out and take care of some things today.
I’m sorry to have to stop right in the middle of a conversation.
But it’s good for now that you can’t see these things.
I think that what you experience is probably similar to sleep paralysis.
I’ll do some research on it until next month.
That’ll be my homework.
Your homework will be keeping a diary.
A diary?
I want you to write about the things you did during the day, and what you thought about.
You don’t have to show it to me.
Just write what you want.
I used to keep a diary when I was your age.
But...
You don't want to?
It can be really interesting to look back on the things you write in your diary.
We can be forgetful, so it can help you remember things, too.
That will cure me?
Hmm.
That probably doesn’t have anything to do with it.
At least it's good for you.
I’ll explain more carefully next month.
I don’t mind if you don’t want to keep a diary.
I went and bought you a diary book, though.
See?
It’s cute, isn’t it?
I found it when I went shopping last week, and I thought it would be a nice present for you.
Thank you.
But don’t force yourself.
You don't have to keep a diary just because I bought you one.
Feel free to write in the diary if you want to, though.
Well I guess we’ll wrap it up, then.
Make sure you’re not forgetting anything.
I’ll walk out to the gate with you.